Guide to the Records of Office of the Vice President for External Affairs and the Office of the Vice President for University Relations, John J. O'Connor RG.7.2
New York University Archives
- Addendum 7/5/2007, 201451
  - NYU Albany Day, 1991-1991; 201501 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Alumni, 1990-1990; 201500 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Awards, 1990-1990; 201499 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Benefits, 1991-1991; 201498 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Chorus, 1992-1992; 201497 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Club, 1989-1993; 201496 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Council, 1990-1992; 201495 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Fundraising, 1993-1994; 201494 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Gifts, 1991-1991; 201493 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Hall, 1989-1990; 201492 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Housing, 1992-1992; 201491 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Federation, 1989-1993; 201490 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Jan-93, 1993-1993; 201489 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Feb-93, 1993-1993; 201488 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Mar-93, 1993-1993; 201487 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Apr-93, 1993-1993; 201486 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - May-93, 1993-1993; 201485 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Jun-93, 1993-1993; 201484 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Jul-93, 1993-1993; 201483 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Aug-93, 1993-1993; 201482 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Sep-93, 1993-1993; 201481 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Oct-93, 1993-1993; 201480 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Nov-93, 1993-1993; 201479 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Dec-93, 1993-1993; 201478 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Master List of Correspondence Files, 1981-1985; 201477 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Files 11/81, 1981; 201476 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Files 1/82 #1, 1982; 201475 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Files 1/82 #2, 1982; 201474 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Files 2/82, 1982; 201473 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Files 3/82, 1982; 201472 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Files 4/82, 1982; 201471 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Files 5/82, 1982; 201470 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Files 6/82, 1982; 201469 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Files 7/82, 1982; 201468 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Files 8/82, 1982; 201467 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Files 9/82, 1982; 201466 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Files 10/82 #1, 1982; 201465 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Files 10/82 #2, 1982; 201464 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Files 11/83, 1983; 201463 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Files 12/83,1/84-2/84, 5/84-6/84, 1983-1984; 201462 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Files 7/84, 1984; 201461 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence Files 8/84, 1984; 201460 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Files 9/84, 1984; 201459 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Files 10/84-11/84, 1984; 201458 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Files 11/84, 1984; 201457 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Files 1/85 #1, 1985; 201456 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Files 1/85 #2, 1985; 201455 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Files 2/85, 1985; 201454 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Files 3/85, 1985; 201453 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Files 6/85, 1985; 201452 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Office for Community Relations, (Formerly RG 3.3)
  - Jog-A-Thon files, 1982-1984 (Box 36)
  - Jog-A-Thon files, 1979-1982 (Box 37)
  - Jog-A-Thon files, George Washington Birthday Ball, 1981 (Box 38)
  - George Washington Birthday Ball, 1981-1984 (Box 39)
  - Washington Square Park: Art Exhibit and Miscellaneous Materials, 1977-1982 (Box 40)
  - Washington Square Fair, 1980-1984 (Box 41)
  - Third Avenue Dormitory Proposals, 1984-1985 (Box 42)
  - Committee for Astor Place, 1978-1984 (Box 43)
  - Committee for Astor Place, Miscellaneous Materials, 1970-1987 (Box 44)